<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>tag:news.dolby.com,2005:/en-WW/press_releases</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://news.dolby.com"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://news.dolby.com/en-WW/press_releases.atom"/>
  <title>Dolby press releases</title>
  <updated>2022-05-03T09:05:00-07:00</updated>
  <logo>https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small_square-1631104740.png</logo>
  <generator uri="http://www.pr.co">pr.co</generator>
  <entry>
    <id>213850</id>
    <published>2022-05-03T09:05:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2022-05-03T09:05:00-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/213850-dolby-laboratories-announces-dr-shriram-revankar-as-svp-advanced-technology-group"/>
    <title type="text">Dolby Laboratories Announces Dr. Shriram Revankar as SVP Advanced Technology Group</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Dolby today announced the appointment of Dr. Shriram Revankar, a technologist and industry leader who has cultivated teams across multiple disciplines to deliver high impact technologies and world-class research, as its Senior Vice President Advanced Technology Group.</strong></p><p> Dolby Laboratories Announces Dr. Shriram Revankar as SVP Advanced Technology Group <p></p><p><b>Seasoned Technologist and Industry Leader brings Decades of Leadership and Innovation to Dolby</b></p><p></p><p><b>SAN FRANCISCO</b> – May 3, 2022 – Dolby Laboratories, Inc. (NYSE:DLB), a leader in immersive entertainment experiences, today announced the appointment of Dr. Shriram Revankar, a technologist and industry leader who has cultivated teams across multiple disciplines to deliver high impact technologies and world-class research, as its Senior Vice President Advanced Technology Group.</p><p> </p><p>Shriram will lead Dolby’s global Advanced Technology Group building on the company’s decades of innovation.</p><p> </p><p>Most recently, as Vice President and Fellow at Adobe, Shriram founded several of Adobe’s global research labs, including the Big-Data Experience Lab and the Document Intelligence Lab. Through these centers he built and led the team that identified and delivered innovations that enabled the growth of Adobe’s Experience Cloud and Document Cloud businesses. As the leader of Adobe’s advanced technology capabilities, he identified and built near-term and future technology needs for multiple businesses and SaaS-based offerings that rely heavily on data science, immersive media experiences, artificial intelligence and computer vision.</p><p> </p><p>“Throughout Shriram’s career he has identified and delivered technology innovations to enable significant business growth for new and established businesses,” said Kevin Yeaman, President and CEO of Dolby Laboratories. “I’m confident that Shriram’s leadership, passion for innovation and domain experience will help fuel Dolby’s future technology offerings and create more immersive experiences.”</p><p> </p><p>“Dolby continuously innovates to deliver the best audio and imaging technologies,” said Dr. Shriram Revankar, Senior Vice President, Dolby Laboratories Advanced Technology Group. “I’m excited to have the opportunity to build on Dolby’s strong product foundation and lead the team inventing the next generation of immersive tools, content and services.”</p><p> </p><p>Prior to joining Adobe, Shriram was a Xerox Fellow and founded and led their Smart and Adaptive Systems Lab.  As Chief Architect of the Production Solutions business at Xerox he developed a platform which enabled integration of multiple independently developed enterprise solutions to interoperate at scale. </p><p> </p><p>Shriram holds a masters and Ph.D. in computer science from SUNY Buffalo. </p><p> </p><p>Steve Forshay, who previously served as the company’s SVP Advanced Technology Group, will support this leadership transition and retire in June. </p><p> </p><p><b>About Dolby Laboratories </b></p><p><a href="https://www.dolby.com/" target="_blank">Dolby Laboratories </a>(NYSE:DLB) is based in San Francisco with offices around the globe. From movies and TV shows, to apps, music, sports, and gaming, Dolby transforms the science of sight and sound into spectacular experiences for billions of people worldwide. We partner with artists, storytellers, developers, and businesses to revolutionize entertainment and communications with <a href="https://www.dolby.com/technologies/dolby-atmos/" target="_blank">Dolby Atmos</a>, <a href="https://www.dolby.com/technologies/dolby-vision/" target="_blank">Dolby Vision</a>, <a href="https://www.dolby.com/movies-tv/cinema" target="_blank">Dolby Cinema</a>, and <a href="https://dolby.io/" target="_blank">Dolby.io</a>. </p><p> </p><p>Dolby, Dolby Atmos, Dolby Vision, Dolby Cinema, Dolby.io, and the double-D symbol are among the registered and unregistered trademarks of Dolby Laboratories, Inc. in the United States and/or other countries. Other trademarks remain the property of their respective owners. </p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/213850-dolby-laboratories-announces-dr-shriram-revankar-as-svp-advanced-technology-group">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>213282</id>
    <published>2022-04-13T19:28:09-07:00</published>
    <updated>2022-04-13T19:28:09-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/213282-naver-launches-world-s-first-dolby-vision-capable-live-commerce-content-opening-a-new-world-for-online-shopping"/>
    <title type="text">Naver launches world’s first Dolby Vision-capable live commerce content, opening a New World for online shopping</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Naver launched a brand-new “Naver Shopping Live” content powered by Dolby Vision imaging technology for the first time in the world. This integration opens new possibilities for how Dolby Vision can be used, while providing customers a new type of virtual shopping experience.</strong></p><p> Naver launches world’s first Dolby Vision-capable live commerce content, opening a New World for online shopping  Dolby Vision brings online shopping closer to the in-person experience by giving shoppers a more lifelike video experience with brighter, more accurate colors and richer details   <p><b>Seoul, Korea, April 14, 2022</b> – Naver launched a brand-new “Naver Shopping Live” content powered by Dolby Vision imaging technology for the first time in the world. This integration opens new possibilities for how Dolby Vision can be used, while providing customers a new type of virtual shopping experience.</p><p> </p><p>Dolby Vision is an industry-leading imaging technology developed by Dolby Laboratories and is embraced by the world’s top creatives. It delivers ultravivid picture quality filled with incredible brightness, contrast, color, and detail. Dolby Vision expands the palette of colors from millions to billions and provides a brightness range up to 100x brighter than a standard video. This results in deeper contrast, lifelike hues, rich detail, and more textures that bring videos to life. </p><p> </p><p>Naver Shopping Live presents the world’s first live commerce content with Dolby Vision, enhancing the experience of consumers and sellers. For sellers and brands, Dolby Vision is a powerful tool for bringing to life the details that make their products unique and are key to the in-person shopping experience, but are difficult to capture and reproduce online -  things like colors, textures, materials, and more. Dolby Vision also ensures that videos are recreated accurately and consistently across almost every type of device and playback scenario where shoppers enjoy Naver content, so sellers can be confident that viewers are seeing the products the way they intend. </p><p> </p><p>For shoppers, this means an overall improved online shopping experience by bringing more of the benefits of in-person shopping to ecommerce. </p><p> </p><p>“Dolby Vision takes our user experience to a new level as it can reproduce vivid colors and textures of products in various industries, like beauty and fashion, where delivering a product’s appearance accurately is critical. We remain committed to developing and advancing technologies to lead the live commerce ecosystem,” said Cho Seong-tak, E-Labs Lead, Naver.</p><p> </p><p>“With demand for live commerce increasing sharply, it is very significant for us to provide high-quality live streaming content never experienced before along with Naver Shopping Live, the nation’s largest live commerce platform, for the first time in the world. <a target="_blank"></a>Dolby Vision, which provides a more realistic online shopping experience by showcasing real hues and textures of the products, will break new ground in the live commerce industry.     ” said<b> </b>Sang Ho Lee, Country Manager at Dolby Laboratories Korea.<b></b></p><p> </p><p>Dolby Vision will be applied first to video content produced at an exclusive studio for Naver Shopping Live, and then will be expanded to other general Shopping Live content. Users can enjoy Shopping Live content in Dolby Vision on diverse enabled devices, through the Naver app for Android or iOS, and Safari browser for Mac OS, while viewing on supported devices. </p><p> </p><p>Naver Shopping Live, a live commerce platform released by Naver in 2020, achieved 700 million cumulative views and about KRW 500 billion in cumulative transaction volume in just 16 months since its launch, positioning itself as the nation’s leading live commerce channel. The newly launched app offers greater user convenience with Naver technologies, including artificial intelligence-based personalized recommendation and AR commerce, in addition to the existing high-speed live streaming, ultra-low latency and automatic captioning features. </p><p> </p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/213282-naver-launches-world-s-first-dolby-vision-capable-live-commerce-content-opening-a-new-world-for-online-shopping">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>209521</id>
    <published>2022-02-03T13:15:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2022-02-03T13:15:00-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/209521-dolby-acquires-millicast-the-real-time-ultra-low-delay-video-streaming-platform"/>
    <title type="text">Dolby acquires Millicast, the real-time, ultra-low-delay video streaming platform</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>The acquisition will complement the Dolby.io platform and enable customers to develop large-scale, highly-interactive online experiences.
</strong></p><p> Dolby acquires Millicast, the real-time, ultra-low-delay video streaming platform  The acquisition will complement the Dolby.io platform and enable customers to develop large-scale, highly-interactive online experiences. <p><b>SAN FRANCISCO – February 3, 2022 </b>– Dolby Laboratories, Inc, (NYSE DLB), a leader in immersive entertainment experiences, today announced the acquisition of Millicast, a developer platform that provides ultra-low-latency video streaming capabilities that scale to massive audiences. </p><p> </p><p>Millicast enables developers to take the highly interactive events they build with Dolby.io, from conferences to music concerts, and stream them from the presenter to audiences of more than 60,000 people with delays of less than 500 milliseconds. Millicast will also bolster Dolby.io WebRTC engineering expertise with a highly-skilled team that has developed standards such as WHIP, which enable WebRTC interoperability. </p><p> </p><p>"There is a growing demand to make online events as lifelike and compelling as being there in person," said Marie Huwe, SVP, Dolby.io. "We are thrilled to welcome the Millicast team to Dolby. Together, we expand the Dolby.io platform to make it even easier for developers and businesses to stream real-time content and immersive, interactive experiences that look and sound incredible." </p><p> </p><p>"Dolby and Millicast share a passion for enabling the future of lightning-fast, crystal-clear content streamed to thousands of participants," said Alexandrine Platonoff, CEO, Millicast. "Together, we have the opportunity to bring ultra-low latency to a global customer base and empower them to build virtualized, massive audience experiences that feel almost as if you were there. We're excited to become a part of Dolby and can't wait to see what we build together." </p><p> </p><p>The vision for Dolby.io is to help developers and businesses achieve stellar audiovisual content and interactive social communications in their applications and services. A vital piece of that vision is the ability to scale quality to the demands of high-volume streaming for virtual events. Dolby has recently made several platform improvements to Dolby.io to support significantly more participants for audio and video, or audio-only. The acquisition of Millicast now brings consistent, field-tested ultra-low-latency so that audiences – small or large – can receive high-quality, interactive experiences.  </p><p> </p><p>Developers can try this out immediately, with sample code, at this <a href="https://dolby.io/blog/live-stream-a-dolby-io-conference-to-millicast" target="_blank">link</a>. </p><p> </p><p>To learn more about Dolby.io and sign up for a free account, please visit <a href="https://dolby.io" target="_blank">https://dolby.io</a>     </p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/209521-dolby-acquires-millicast-the-real-time-ultra-low-delay-video-streaming-platform">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>207712</id>
    <published>2021-12-08T05:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-08T05:30:00-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/207712-dolby-appoints-tony-prophet-to-its-board-of-directors"/>
    <title type="text">Dolby Appoints Tony Prophet to its Board of Directors</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Dolby announced today the appointment of Tony Prophet to its Board of Directors, effective December 6, 2021. </strong></p><p> Dolby Appoints Tony Prophet to its Board of Directors <p>SAN FRANCISCO, December 8, 2021 ­– Dolby Laboratories, Inc. (NYSE:DLB) announced today the appointment of Tony Prophet to its Board of Directors, effective December 6, 2021. Over the course of many years, Tony has established himself as a technology industry leader who has helped guide companies across multiple disciplines. </p><p> </p><p>Most recently, Tony served as the Chief Equality and Recruiting Officer at Salesforce, co-chairing the Salesforce Racial Equality and Justice Task Force, created to help drive systemic change in the workplace and community. He was also a co-founder of the company's Ethical and Humane Use of technology initiative. During his time with Microsoft, Tony served as Corporate Vice President, Education Marketing, Corporate Vice President of Windows and Search Marketing, and Corporate Vice President of Windows Marketing. Prior to Microsoft, he held leadership roles at HP, including leading worldwide PC and printing operations, and previously served in positions of increasing responsibility at multiple organizations, including leading worldwide operations for the Carrier Business unit of United Technologies and rising to Partner at Booz Allen Hamilton.</p><p> </p><p>“We are excited to welcome Tony to the Board of Directors,” said Peter Gotcher, Chairman of the Dolby Board of Directors. “His combination of leadership and management experience, dedication to equality and inclusion, and passion for Dolby will bring tremendous value to the Dolby Board.”</p><p> </p><p>“I’m incredibly impressed with Dolby’s leadership team,” said Tony Prophet. “Dolby technologies transform how developers and content creators deliver high-quality, interactive and media-centric applications, and how billions of people worldwide experience their entertainment. I look forward to working with the Dolby team to help drive the company’s future growth and support the communities in which they do business.”</p><p> </p><p>Additional details regarding the appointment can be found in a Current Report on Form 8-K filed by Dolby today with the Securities and Exchange Commission.</p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/207712-dolby-appoints-tony-prophet-to-its-board-of-directors">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>206271</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T05:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-01T05:30:00-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/206271-new-survey-from-dolby-reveals-shifts-in-music-listening-behavior-among-adults-in-the-u-s"/>
    <title type="text">New Survey from Dolby Reveals Shifts in Music Listening Behavior Among Adults in the U.S. </title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Dolby released new findings from a new survey illustrating a shift in music listening behavior. </strong></p><p> New Survey from Dolby Reveals Shifts in Music Listening Behavior  Among Adults in the U.S.   Nearly 70% of Gen Z have recently discovered a song released over a decade ago for the first time.    More than half of adults feel they were born in the wrong era because of their taste in music, and for most, the 2000s best match their music preferences.  Nearly 90% believe enhanced audio quality is a “must-have” when streaming music, and 80% of those upgraded or changed services to one with better quality. <p> </p><p><b>SAN FRANCISCO</b> – December 1, 2021 – Dolby Laboratories, Inc. (NYSE: DLB), a leader in immersive entertainment experiences, released findings from a new survey illustrating a shift in music listening behavior. The U.S. study of adults (18+ or older) who regularly listen to music found that many, particularly Gen Z, have recently discovered iconic songs and artists from past decades for the first time while others are rediscovering songs from their past. The research revealed social media and Hollywood entertainment have a strong influence over how people discover music. In addition, the study also found that better audio quality is a priority for many, particularly Gen Z, when choosing a streaming subscription over other features. </p><p></p><p>“Music fills our lives with moments of joy and has been a way to escape the challenges we have faced over the past two years. This has driven changes in consumer behavior, such as the revival of music from past decades to the prioritization of better-quality experiences that allow listeners to connect more deeply with their favorite artists and songs,” said John Couling, Senior Vice President of Entertainment at Dolby Laboratories. “As we look to the future, we expect these influences to have a lasting impact over how we enjoy music.”</p><p></p><p>The US-based survey, conducted by OnePoll in November 2021, polled 2,000 general population adults who regularly listen to music for at least one hour per day. The survey examined their listening behavior, purchase decisions, and habits formed from the COVID-19 pandemic.</p><p> </p><p><b>U.S. adults are feeling nostalgic based on their choices in music</b></p><p>A number of respondents feel like they were born in the wrong era because of their taste in music, which was highest among Gen Z. This has led to the increased popularity of iconic songs and artists being rediscovered or discovered for the first time.</p><p></p><p></p><ul><li><b>Six in 10</b> feel like they were born in the wrong era because of their taste in music, which was highest among Gen Z (<b>nearly 80%</b>). For most, the era that most closely matches their taste in music was <b>the 2000s.</b></li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>Almost half </b>have recently discovered a song released over a decade ago, which was highest among Gen Z respondents (<b>nearly 70%</b>).</li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>Almost half</b> stated they had rediscovered an iconic song or album within the past two years, particularly<b> Gen Z</b> (over two-thirds). </li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>Most respondents</b>, close to 70%, are embarrassed to share their music playlists with others, particularly<b> their boss.</b> </li></ul><p></p><p><b>Social media and Hollywood entertainment heavily influence the discovery of new music </b></p><p>Social media is the most significant influence shaping how people discover new music, while movies and TV shows play an equally important role. </p><p></p><p></p><ul><li><b>57%</b> said social media is the top way they discover music.</li></ul><p></p><ul><li>While YouTube is the<b> most popular platform </b>for discovering music, according to 79% surveyed, <b>Facebook, Instagram, and TikTok</b> significantly influence how people find new songs. </li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>Almost a fourth </b>of people who recently discovered a song released over a decade ago attribute this discovery to a viral video on social media.  </li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>Six in 10</b> have also discovered a new artist or song after watching a TV show or movie. </li></ul><p></p><p><b>People in the U.S. are spending more time and money on music </b></p><p>Music has been a vehicle for escapism as many now spend more time and money on music than they were at the start of 2020. </p><p></p><p></p><ul><li><b>Over two-thirds</b> spend more time listening to music each day than before the start of 2020, with <b>over half</b> listening to music <b>four hours per day or more</b>.</li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>55%</b> indicated that they spend more money on music purchases each month, such as streaming subscriptions, than at the start of 2020.</li></ul><p></p><p><b>Many are prioritizing audio quality when enjoying music</b></p><p>When choosing a music streaming plan, music fans prioritize quality above all – especially Gen Z. This insight coincides with broader industry trends around the uptick among streaming services that offer subscribers enhanced audio through spatial audio experiences like Dolby Atmos or high resolution (HD) audio.</p><p></p><p></p><ul><li>Among those who pay for a music streaming plan, <b>nearly 90%</b> agreed that enhanced audio quality is a “must-have” feature of their subscription, of which <b>more than half</b> <b>strongly agreed</b>.</li><li>Of this group, <b>82%</b> have upgraded, changed subscriptions, or explicitly paid for a service because it offered better audio quality.</li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>Nearly two-thirds </b>who pay for a music streaming subscription indicated that better sound quality was <b>more important</b> than other features such as ad-free listening, exclusive content, or the ability to add multiple users to their account.</li><li><b>Over 70%</b> surveyed are likely or very likely to purchase a new audio device within the next six months specifically to enhance their experience when listening to music. </li></ul><p></p><p>Preference for better audio quality was notably high among Gen Z:</p><p></p><ul><li><b>Nearly half </b>of Gen Z surveyed who pay for a music streaming subscription want access to the latest cutting-edge audio technologies with their plan. </li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>86% of Gen Z surveyed </b>are likely to purchase a new audio device in the next six months to get better audio quality when enjoying music.</li></ul><p></p><p>The survey also uncovered:</p><p></p><ul><li>Comparing various types of in-car entertainment, most see the biggest opportunity for enhancing the listening experience <b>when enjoying music</b> in the car (43%), followed by audiobooks and podcasts (23%).</li></ul><p></p><ul><li><b>More than two-thirds</b> stated they were very interested or somewhat interested in a new technology that lets them experience music more deeply when driving. </li></ul><p><b>Incredible music listening experiences in Dolby Atmos are more accessible than ever </b></p><p>With many adults prioritizing audio quality, streaming services look to technologies like Dolby Atmos to meet this demand and offer subscribers a differentiated experience. At the same time, Dolby Atmos has been used by creatives to introduce, or reintroduce, their music to new audiences. </p><p> </p><p>“Dolby Atmos empowers artists to push their artistry to new limits by expanding the palette of what is creatively possible. As a fan, there is no comparison to hearing music in Dolby Atmos for the first time,” said John Couling, Senior Vice President of Entertainment at Dolby Laboratories. “Listening to songs in Dolby Atmos is a visceral experience that completely changes how you want to enjoy music.”</p><p> </p><p>Music fans can enjoy Dolby Atmos today through popular music streaming services like <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2021/05/apple-music-announces-spatial-audio-and-lossless-audio/" target="_blank">Apple Music</a>. Dolby has also worked with MGM Resorts International to launch <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203399-dolby-and-mgm-resorts-international-launch-dolby-live-at-park-mgm-bringing-live-music-performances-in-dolby-atmos-to-the-entertainment" target="_blank">Dolby Live at Park MGM</a>, the world’s first performance venue of its kind to offer live concerts in Dolby Atmos. Dolby Atmos is also transforming music listening inside cars through recent partnerships with <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/197447-lucid-air-is-the-world-s-first-vehicle-to-integrate-dolby-atmos" target="_blank">Lucid Motors</a>, <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203864-mercedes-benz-ag-gears-up-to-bring-dolby-atmos-music-experience-to-its-cars" target="_blank">Mercedes-Benz</a>, and <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/204730-nio-et7-comes-standard-with-dolby-atmos" target="_blank">NIO</a>.</p><p> </p><p>For information about how to enjoy Dolby Atmos, visit: <a href="https://www.dolby.com/music/" target="_blank">https://www.dolby.com/music/</a> <b> </b></p><p></p><p>Survey Methodology</p><p>This random double-opt-in survey of <b>2,000 general population adults in the U.S.</b> was commissioned by <b>Dolby</b> between <b>November 10</b> and <b>November 12</b>, <b>2021</b>. It was conducted by market research company <a href="https://www.onepoll.us/" target="_blank">OnePoll</a>, whose team members are members of the <a href="https://www.mrs.org.uk/" target="_blank">Market Research Society</a> and have corporate membership to the American Association for Public Opinion Research (<a href="https://www.aapor.org/" target="_blank">AAPOR</a>) and the European Society for Opinion and Marketing Research (<a href="https://www.esomar.org/" target="_blank">ESOMAR</a>).</p><p><b> </b></p><p><b>About Dolby Atmos Music</b></p><p>Dolby Atmos is an immersive audio technology, which is transforming how music is created and experienced. It takes music to new levels by immersing listeners inside the song to reveal details with unparalleled clarity and depth. Whether it’s hearing the layers of instruments move all around, catching the subtle breath a singer takes between lyrics, or being enveloped in a wave of melodies, nothing compares to hearing music in Dolby Atmos. </p><p> </p><p>To learn more, check out Dolby’s recent consumer campaign celebrating Dolby Atmos Music. The campaign features five of the most prominent artists in the world – <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202293-billie-eilish-s-happier-than-ever-a-love-letter-to-los-angeles-available-today-on-disney-in-dolby-vision-and-dolby-atmos" target="_blank">Billie Eilish</a>, <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202509-dolby-and-j-balvin-team-up-to-explore-how-music-can-elevate-joy" target="_blank">J Balvin</a>, <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202532-dolby-and-justin-bieber-team-up-to-go-inside-the-story-of-his-latest-single-ghost" target="_blank">Justin Bieber</a>, <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202533-dolby-and-multi-platinum-singer-songwriter-olivia-rodrigo-team-up-to-share-an-intimate-look-at-her-hit-song-traitor" target="_blank">Olivia Rodrigo</a>, and <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202531-dolby-teams-up-with-the-weeknd-to-explore-how-he-creates-worlds-with-music" target="_blank">The Weeknd</a> – who share why they think Dolby Atmos is ushering in a new era for music. </p><p></p><p></p><p></p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/206271-new-survey-from-dolby-reveals-shifts-in-music-listening-behavior-among-adults-in-the-u-s">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>204730</id>
    <published>2021-11-15T16:27:25-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-11-15T16:27:25-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/204730-nio-et7-comes-standard-with-dolby-atmos"/>
    <title type="text">NIO ET7 Comes Standard with Dolby Atmos</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>NIO announced that Dolby Atmos will come standard on all NIO ET7s.</strong></p><p> NIO ET7 Comes Standard with Dolby Atmos <p><b>Shanghai </b>– On Nov. 16, NIO announced that Dolby Atmos will come standard on all NIO ET7s, the smart flagship electric sedan of the company, and when combined with the vehicle's 7.1.4 immersive sound system, will bring the in-car audio experience beyond users’ expectation.</p><p></p><p>Dolby Atmos is a completely new way to create and experience music that delivers artistic expression at its fullest capacity, forging a deeper connection between artists and their fans. Widely embraced by leading artists and creatives, record labels, and music streaming services, music in Dolby Atmos goes beyond the ordinary listening experience by fully immersing the audience, revealing details with unparalleled clarity and depth. It gives artists more space and the freedom to fully realize their vision and unlocks new levels of emotion in their music for their listeners.   </p><p> </p><p>The ET7’s audio system comes standard with 23 speakers and a total output of 1000W. The four primary channels use a 3-way speaker array which features dedicated tweeter, mid-tone and bass driver, a subwoofer plus four overhead speakers. Combining a leading active tuning algorithm and Dolby Atmos’ excellent detail and clarity, the ET7 provides an immersive listening experience beyond users’ expectation.</p><p> </p><p>Mark Zhou, NIO’s Executive Vice President and Chairman of the Product Committee, said, “NIO aims to keep improving the value of the car apart from driving and riding, and creating surprises for users through the integration of technological progress and emotional experience. The collaboration between Dolby and NIO will make users more deeply bonded with the music they love, and jointly push forward the in-car experience.”</p><p></p><p>John Couling, Senior Vice President, Entertainment, Dolby Laboratories, said, “We are excited to extend the future of car audio to consumers in China and internationally by integrating Dolby Atmos in the ET7. Music is an important aspect of the in-car experience. Whether you want to immerse yourself in the music or simply complement your drive – once you experience the subtle detail and raw power of Dolby Atmos – music in your car will never be the same. We cannot wait to bring that extraordinary listening experience to users with the ET7.”</p><p> </p><p>The ET7 is now available for pre-order through the NIO app and the deliveries are estimated to begin in Q1 2022.</p><p> </p><p>Alongside today’s ET7 announcement, NIO Radio, an exclusive Radio for NIO users, will also support Dolby Atmos. NIO Radio, free from geographical boundaries, aims at providing a third way of getting connected in the community of NIO users, after NIO App and NIO House have connected NIO user community online and offline. NIO users can look forward to enjoying the auditory feast on the ET7 by subscribing to NIO Radio's Dolby Atmos program.</p><p> </p><p><b>About</b><b> NIO Inc.</b></p><p> </p><p>NIO Inc. is a global smart electric vehicle company. Founded in November 2014, NIO’s mission is to shape a joyful lifestyle by offering high-performance smart electric vehicles and being the best user enterprise. NIO has established R&amp;D centers and manufacturing facilities in Shanghai, Hefei, Beijing, Nanjing, San Jose, Munich, Oxford and other places, and has initially set up the user service network with nationwide coverage in China.</p><p> </p><p>In 2015, NIO Formula E team won the inaugural FIA Formula E Drivers’ Championship; in 2016, NIO launched EP9, one of the world’s fastest electric vehicles, which broke lap records and the world’s autonomous driving records in global-famous tracks like the Nürburgring Nordschleife; in 2017, NIO unveiled the vision car EVE. On June 28, 2018, NIO began deliveries of the ES8, a 7-seater high-performance smart electric flagship SUV, in China. On September 12, 2018, NIO went public on NYSE. NIO officially launched the ES6, a 5-seater all-round smart electric SUV, on December 15, 2018 and started its deliveries on June 18, 2019. In December 2019, NIO officially launched the EC6, a smart electric Coupe SUV, and the all-new ES8, a fully elevated smart electric flagship SUV. On April 19, 2020, NIO began the first deliveries of the all-new ES8. On April 29, 2020, NIO China established its headquarters in Hefei Economic and Technological Development Area. On July 24, 2020, NIO officially launched the EC6, a smart electric Coupe SUV, and began deliveries of the EC6 in September 2020. On January 9, 2021, NIO ET7, the smart electric flagship sedan with autonomous driving capability, was officially launched.</p><p> </p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/204730-nio-et7-comes-standard-with-dolby-atmos">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>204503</id>
    <published>2021-11-10T15:15:06-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-11-10T15:15:06-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/204503-dolby-introduces-new-and-improved-dolby-io-spatial-audio-feature-for-developers"/>
    <title type="text">Dolby introduces new and improved Dolby.io Spatial Audio feature for developers </title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Introducing the new and improved Spatial Audio feature, now with Spatial Placement, as part of the Dolby.io Communications SDK.</strong></p><p> Dolby introduces new and improved Dolby.io Spatial Audio feature for developers   New Spatial Placement capability will enable developers and businesses to build more lifelike listening experiences into their apps and services  <p>SAN FRANCISCO – November 10, 2021 – Dolby Laboratories, Inc, (NYSE DLB) a leader in immersive entertainment experiences, today introduced the new and improved Spatial Audio feature, now with Spatial Placement, as part of the Dolby.io Communications SDK. Available in closed beta, Spatial Placement enables developers to place audio objects anywhere within a virtualized three-dimensional space. With the addition of the Spatial Placement capability, the Dolby.io Communications SDK – powered by the award-winning Dolby Voice technology – will help businesses and developers build high-fidelity, natural, real-time audio and communications experiences. To learn more and sign up for the closed beta, please visit: <a href="http://go.dolby.io/spatial-audio" target="_blank">http://go.dolby.io/spatial-audio</a>  </p><p> </p><p>The way people interact online – and work – has fundamentally changed. For consumers and members of distributed workforces, mono audio and basic voice capabilities are no longer sufficient for an online populace that increasingly demands higher quality, lifelike experiences.  </p><p> </p><p>With the improved Spatial Audio feature, developers and businesses can go beyond the traditionally flat nature of virtual conversations to configure and place audio exactly where it’s supposed to sound. Whether it’s an online classroom, a video conference, or even a performance, the addition of Spatial Placement makes it so that, for example, if a speaker is on the left side of the screen, that’s where the listener hears them speak. This kind of technology can help participants of these virtualized environments engage in more natural conversation and better understand each other.  </p><p> </p><p>“People are yearning for more lifelike experiences in their professional and day-to-day online activities,” said Paul Boustead, Vice President of Product and Architecture, Dolby.io, Dolby Laboratories. “With the new and improved Spatial Audio feature, we’re continuing to expand the scope of opportunity for businesses and developers who want to build experiences that sound incredible. We can’t wait to hear what they come up with.”  </p><p> </p><p>Spatial Audio is a feature of the Dolby.io Communications SDK and will support Dolby.io Video Calls, Voice Calls, and Call Recording. It offers the following benefits:  </p><p> </p><p><b>Configurable </b></p><p>Assign each sound file or source to a specific location in a virtualized, three-dimensional space inside of a web or mobile application.  </p><p> </p><p><b>Adaptive  </b></p><p>Map to any cartesian coordinate system for use in building and placing audio inside an application.  </p><p> </p><p><b>No added costs </b></p><p>Access the new Spatial Audio feature at no additional cost. Simply enable the feature within the Dolby.io Communications SDK. </p><p> </p><p>“<a href="http://dolby.io/" target="_blank">Dolby.io</a>  already allows Boardroom One to provide dynamic, real-time, and crystal-clear conversations, where no one gets cut off and speakers engage in a much more natural discussion.” said Pablos Holman, founder of Boardroom One. “We can’t wait to try out the new and improved Spatial Audio feature in order to deliver a user experience closer to real-life conversation.” </p><p>  </p><p>To learn more and sign up for the Spatial Placement closed beta, please visit: <a href="http://go.dolby.io/spatial-audio" target="_blank">http://go.dolby.io/spatial-audio</a> </p><p> </p><p></p><p>  </p><p></p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/204503-dolby-introduces-new-and-improved-dolby-io-spatial-audio-feature-for-developers">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>203864</id>
    <published>2021-10-28T01:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-10-28T01:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203864-mercedes-benz-ag-gears-up-to-bring-dolby-atmos-music-experience-to-its-cars"/>
    <title type="text">Mercedes-Benz AG gears up to bring Dolby Atmos Music experience to its cars</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Mercedes is set to offer ultimate in car audio to it's range of cars with Dolby Atmos </strong></p><p> Mercedes-Benz AG gears up to bring Dolby Atmos Music experience to its cars <p>Stuttgart/Munich – Mercedes-Benz today announced that it will be offering Dolby Atmos® in a range of its top car models providing the ultimate in-car audio experience to its customers, allowing listeners to connect with music to its fullest creative potential. </p><p></p><p>The Dolby Atmos experience will be built into the optional Burmester® high-end 4D and 3D sound system as well as integrated into the Mercedes-Maybach and shortly afterwards in the Mercedes-Benz S-Class, turning the Mercedes-Benz vehicles into state-of-the-art concert halls on wheels. </p><p></p><p>Powered by a total of 31 loudspeakers and eight sound transducers, also known as exciters, which will also be mounted into the seats, audiophiles will receive an unprecedented sound experience as they take the wheel of their chosen car, offering them a whole new immersive soundscape as they take to the road. </p><p></p><p>“Our customers rightly expect the highest level of music enjoyment in a Mercedes-Benz vehicle. Therefore, Mercedes-Benz is one of the first luxury car brands in the world to rely on the ground-breaking Dolby Atmos technology”, says Britta Seeger, Member of the Board of Management of Daimler AG and Mercedes-Benz AG responsible for Sales. ”With Dolby Atmos and the Burmester sound system, we offer our customers an exciting music experience in the vehicle that is almost like a live concert. I am sure the customers will be delighted.” </p><p></p><p>The entertainment hardware of the Burmester® high-end 4D sound system installed in the Maybach and the S-Class already includes: </p><p></p><p></p><ul><li>31 speakers, including 6 3D speakers that emit their sound from above, 4 near-ear speakers in the front seats, an 18.5-liter subwoofer </li><li>8 sound transducers (two per seat) </li><li>2 amplifiers </li><li>1750 watts power</li></ul><p></p><p>John Couling, Senior Vice President Commercial Partnerships, Dolby Laboratories said: “At Dolby we are passionate about extending the Dolby Atmos Music experience so that consumers can enjoy it anywhere and Mercedes-Benz shares our vision. We are excited to be collaborating with them to accelerate the adoption of this immersive auditory experience in cars. The integration of Dolby Atmos into the S-Class and the Mercedes-Maybach will offer an additional superior feature to customers whether they are in the driving seat or a passenger.” </p><p></p><p>An immersive audio experience, Dolby Atmos Music adds more space, clarity and depth to music. The technology empowers creators to place discrete audio elements or objects in a three-dimensional sound field, which goes beyond the capabilities of mono or stereo. </p><p></p><p>Dolby Atmos adapts to any playback environment, meaning fans can listen to music with unparalleled clarity that matches an artist’s original vision in the studio. </p><p></p><p>The Maybach, which incorporates Dolby Atmos, is one of the first cars in the world and the first model in the Mercedes-Benz Cars line-up to offer this superior, multidimensional sound experience that ideally complements the brand's other luxury features. Luxury has always been part of Mercedes-Benz’s DNA and remains a timeless concept, though one that is constantly evolving. Mercedes-Benz strives to shape the future of luxury with heritage and a progressive vision, it’s about the extraordinary that creates desire. As a result, the Maybach is even better able to appeal to all its passengers' senses at the highest level. The Dolby Atmos integrated in the Mercedes-Maybach will be available starting summer 2022 and will be offered for other models shortly thereafter equipped with the new MBUX system introduced with the new Mercedes- Benz S-Class. </p><p></p><p></p><p>Mercedes-Benz AG at a glance </p><p>Mercedes-Benz AG is responsible for the global business of Mercedes-Benz Cars and Mercedes-Benz Vans, with over 170,000 employees worldwide. Ola Källenius is Chairman of the Board of Management of Mercedes-Benz AG. The company focuses on the development, production and sales of passenger cars, vans and vehicle-related services. Furthermore, the company aspires to be the leader in the fields of electric mobility and vehicle software. The product portfolio comprises the Mercedes-Benz brand with the brands of Mercedes-AMG, Mercedes-Maybach, Mercedes-EQ, G-Class and the smart brand. The Mercedes me brand offers access to the digital services from Mercedes-Benz. Mercedes-Benz AG is one of the world's largest manufacturers of luxury passenger cars. In 2020 it sold around 2.1 million passenger cars and nearly 375,000 vans. In its two business segments, Mercedes-Benz AG is continually expanding its worldwide production network with around 35 production sites on four continents, while gearing itself to meet the requirements of electric mobility. At the same time, the company is constructing and extending its global battery production network on three continents. As sustainability is the guiding principle of the Mercedes-Benz strategy and for the company itself, this means creating lasting value for all stakeholders: for customers, employees, investors, business partners and society as a whole. The basis for this is Daimler's sustainable business strategy. The company thus takes responsibility for the economic, ecological and social effects of its business activities and looks at the entire value chain.             </p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203864-mercedes-benz-ag-gears-up-to-bring-dolby-atmos-music-experience-to-its-cars">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>203425</id>
    <published>2021-10-15T09:07:05-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-10-15T09:07:05-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203425-robert-park-joins-dolby-laboratories-as-chief-financial-officer"/>
    <title type="text">Robert Park Joins Dolby Laboratories as Chief Financial Officer </title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Dolby today announced the appointment of Robert Park, a global finance leader with  a track record of guiding companies through growth, as its Senior Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</strong></p><p> Robert Park Joins Dolby Laboratories as Chief Financial Officer   Seasoned Executive Brings Decades of Financial and Business Leadership to Dolby <p><b>SAN FRANCISCO</b> – October 15, 2021 – Dolby Laboratories, Inc. (NYSE:DLB), a leader in immersive entertainment experiences, today announced the appointment of Robert Park, a global finance leader with  a track record of guiding companies through growth, as its Senior Vice President and Chief Financial Officer.</p><p> </p><p>Robert will lead Dolby’s global finance organization building on the company’s strong financial position.  As previously announced, Lewis Chew, the company’s Chief Financial Officer since 2012, will support this leadership transition and retire at the end of the calendar year. </p><p> </p><p>“Throughout Robert’s career he has implemented financial strategies to accelerate decision making, navigate changing landscapes and help companies achieve their near-and long-term objectives, all while delivering operational excellence and accountability,” said Kevin Yeaman, President and CEO of Dolby Laboratories. “I’m confident that Robert’s leadership combined with his financial and business expertise will support our company’s next phase of growth.”</p><p> </p><p>“Dolby is enabling a growing number of experiences for people around the world,” said Robert Park, SVP and Chief Financial Officer Dolby Laboratories. “As the company expands how people can have Dolby experiences,  it’s an incredible opportunity to design the financial strategies that will enable future revenue growth and deliver shareholder value.”</p><p> </p><p>Most recently, as Chief Financial Officer of BlueJeans, Robert played a key role in shaping and executing on the cloud platform’s growth strategy. During his tenure, the company delivered improved operating margins which ultimately led to the 2020 acquisition by Verizon.  </p><p> </p><p>Throughout Robert’s career, including BlueJeans, Chegg Inc., and PayPal, he’s developed and led teams that collaborate with multiple business units to create financial strategies across key business drivers - from sales productivity and marketing program efficacy to product and development prioritization to facilitated business alignment - to enable the delivery of top-line growth and improved profitability.</p><p> </p><p>In accounting and leadership roles at Ernst &amp; Young, where he served numerous technology clients, and McKesson Corporation Robert delivered operational excellence and accountability. </p><p> </p><p>Robert earned his degree in Business Administration with a concentration in accounting from California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo. </p><p> </p><p><b>About  Dolby Laboratories</b></p><p><a href="https://www.dolby.com/" target="_blank">Dolby Laboratories </a>(NYSE:DLB) is based in San Francisco with offices around the globe. From movies and TV shows, to apps, music, sports, and gaming, Dolby transforms the science of sight and sound into spectacular experiences for billions of people worldwide. We partner with artists, storytellers, developers, and businesses to revolutionize entertainment and communications with <a href="https://www.dolby.com/technologies/dolby-atmos/" target="_blank">Dolby Atmos</a>, <a href="https://www.dolby.com/technologies/dolby-vision/" target="_blank">Dolby Vision</a>, <a href="https://www.dolby.com/movies-tv/cinema" target="_blank">Dolby Cinema</a>, and <a href="https://dolby.io/" target="_blank">Dolby.io</a>. </p><p> </p><p>Dolby, Dolby Atmos, Dolby Vision, Dolby Cinema, Dolby.io, and the double-D symbol are among the registered and unregistered trademarks of Dolby Laboratories, Inc. in the United States and/or other countries. Other trademarks remain the property of their respective owners. </p><p> </p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203425-robert-park-joins-dolby-laboratories-as-chief-financial-officer">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>203399</id>
    <published>2021-10-14T05:30:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-10-14T05:30:00-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203399-dolby-and-mgm-resorts-international-launch-dolby-live-at-park-mgm-bringing-live-music-performances-in-dolby-atmos-to-the-entertainment"/>
    <title type="text">Dolby and MGM Resorts International Launch Dolby Live at Park MGM, Bringing Live Music Performances in Dolby Atmos to the Entertainment Capital of the World</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="Dolby" src="https://d21buns5ku92am.cloudfront.net/68658/logo/small-1631104740.png" /><p><strong>Dolby and MGM Resorts International announce the launch of Dolby Live at Park MGM, the first fully integrated performance venue of its kind to offer live concerts in Dolby Atmos.</strong></p><p> Dolby and MGM Resorts International Launch Dolby Live at Park MGM, Bringing Live Music Performances in Dolby Atmos to the Entertainment Capital of the World  Dolby Live is the first performance venue of its kind to feature a fully integrated Dolby Atmos music experience <p><i>*Illustrative image of Dolby Live at Park MGM</i></p><p></p><p><b>SAN FRANCISCO AND LAS VEGAS </b>– October 14, 2021 – Dolby Laboratories, Inc. (NYSE: DLB), a leader in immersive entertainment experiences, and MGM Resorts International (NYSE: MGM), a global leader in live entertainment and hospitality, announced the launch of Dolby Live at Park MGM, the first fully integrated performance venue of its kind to offer live concerts in Dolby Atmos. Located in the heart of the Las Vegas Strip, Dolby Live (formerly known as Park Theater) is the preeminent location for live music in Dolby Atmos, which offers guests a transformative music experience they won’t be able to find anywhere else in the world.</p><p> </p><p>“Joining our slate of premier offerings for immersive entertainment, such as the Dolby Theater in Hollywood and the hundreds of Dolby Cinemas around the world, Dolby Live is the ultimate experience for enjoying live music in Dolby Atmos,” said Kevin Yeaman, President and CEO, Dolby Laboratories. “As we continue to grow our presence in music, Dolby Live will offer consumers more ways to enjoy a Dolby Atmos experience while deepening and expanding our engagements with the artist community.”</p><p> </p><p>Dolby and MGM Resorts have worked closely over the past months to completely transform Dolby Live into one of the world’s most technologically advanced performance installations. The space now features a fully integrated Dolby Atmos playback system, which was designed, calibrated, and tuned by Dolby engineers to match the size and unique characteristics of the 5,200-seat theater. While the system will be primarily used for live concerts, it has the capability to support a multitude of live events in Dolby Atmos such as musicals, eSport events, and much more. </p><p> </p><p>“Dolby Live is a new immersive live music experience where the audience will feel like they are literally on stage with their favorite artist,” said Todd Pendleton, Senior Vice President and Chief Marketing Officer, Dolby Laboratories. “Dolby Atmos is at the center of this new experience, which is transforming how music is created and enjoyed. There is no better way to enjoy live entertainment than in Dolby.”</p><p> </p><p>Dolby Atmos is an immersive audio technology enabling the greatest entertainment across cinema, streaming, gaming, sports, and music. At Dolby Live, Dolby Atmos takes live performances to the next level by taking listeners inside the music to reveal details with unparalleled clarity and depth. Whether it’s hearing the layers of instruments move all around, catching the subtle breath a singer takes between lyrics, or being enveloped in a wave of melodies, nothing compares to hearing music live in Dolby Atmos. </p><p> </p><p>Bill Hornbuckle, CEO and President of MGM Resorts International, said, “One of The Strip’s premier resort destinations, Park MGM is home to some of the biggest names in music. Collaborating with Dolby to revolutionize our live entertainment offerings takes the experience to entirely new levels. Dolby Live will be the most advanced performance venue on The Strip, reflecting our commitment to innovation and creativity in all we do.”</p><p> </p><p>To learn more, visit <a href="https://www.dolby.com/dolby-live-mgm/" target="_blank">https://www.dolby.com/dolby-live-mgm/</a> </p><p> </p><p><b>Dolby Atmos Music</b></p><p>The launch of Dolby Live follows the debut of Dolby’s recent consumer campaign celebrating Dolby Atmos Music, a completely new way to create and experience music that delivers artistic expression at its fullest capacity, forging a deeper connection between artists and their fans. The campaign features five of the biggest names in music – <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202293-billie-eilish-s-happier-than-ever-a-love-letter-to-los-angeles-available-today-on-disney-in-dolby-vision-and-dolby-atmos" target="_blank">Billie Eilish</a>, <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202509-dolby-and-j-balvin-team-up-to-explore-how-music-can-elevate-joy" target="_blank">J Balvin</a>, <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202532-dolby-and-justin-bieber-team-up-to-go-inside-the-story-of-his-latest-single-ghost" target="_blank">Justin Bieber</a>, <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202533-dolby-and-multi-platinum-singer-songwriter-olivia-rodrigo-team-up-to-share-an-intimate-look-at-her-hit-song-traitor" target="_blank">Olivia Rodrigo</a>, and <a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/202531-dolby-teams-up-with-the-weeknd-to-explore-how-he-creates-worlds-with-music" target="_blank">The Weeknd</a> – and spotlights why they believe Dolby Atmos is ushering a new era for music. Dolby Atmos gives artists more space and the freedom to fully realize their vision and unlock new levels of emotion in their music for their listeners. </p><p> </p><p><b>Dolby Live</b></p><p>Dolby Live is a 5,200-seat theater and the world’s first entertainment venue of its kind fully integrated to support live performances in Dolby Atmos. Located inside Park MGM in Las Vegas, Dolby Live hosts a variety of events ranging from live concerts to comedy shows to sporting events and awards shows – in addition to special musical performances in Dolby Atmos. Dolby Live is home to special engagements by Lady Gaga, Bruno Mars, Aerosmith, and Cher, among others. Upcoming performances in Dolby Atmos will be announced at a later date. For Dolby Live show and ticket information, including a list of upcoming events in Dolby Atmos, visit <a href="http://www.parktheaterlv.com/" target="_blank">ParkMGM.com</a> or follow on <a href="https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=http-3A__www.facebook.com_parkmgm&amp;d=DwMFAg&amp;c=lI8Zb6TzM3d1tX4iEu7bpg&amp;r=TGOB-Otu1zgR_-ymSsP-25wwVEWOnfT3q_BT7TF87aI&amp;m=vRXzzeHRwqga6nQzi1_GXx6kg-LoeenUs0yxCMcYY8E&amp;s=5-foOGtv6m4hqI_eZEaHEnPucLADypOihCSsVrAA8TY&amp;e=" target="_blank">Facebook</a><u>,</u> <a href="https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=http-3A__www.twitter.com_parkmgm&amp;d=DwMFAg&amp;c=lI8Zb6TzM3d1tX4iEu7bpg&amp;r=TGOB-Otu1zgR_-ymSsP-25wwVEWOnfT3q_BT7TF87aI&amp;m=vRXzzeHRwqga6nQzi1_GXx6kg-LoeenUs0yxCMcYY8E&amp;s=kw5HRccFWjFRL9CoBI3aKt53KCAkQUyWzEKe3AnZUHg&amp;e=" target="_blank">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=https-3A__www.instagram.com_parkmgm_&amp;d=DwMFAg&amp;c=lI8Zb6TzM3d1tX4iEu7bpg&amp;r=TGOB-Otu1zgR_-ymSsP-25wwVEWOnfT3q_BT7TF87aI&amp;m=vRXzzeHRwqga6nQzi1_GXx6kg-LoeenUs0yxCMcYY8E&amp;s=cu9VKo6sQ3-vigKwK9CWrMW8KV4UlYgU7PmdppHwYzg&amp;e=" target="_blank">Instagram</a>.</p><p></p><p><b>About MGM Resorts International</b></p><p>MGM Resorts International (NYSE: MGM) is an S&amp;P 500® global entertainment company with national and international locations featuring best-in-class hotels and casinos, state-of-the-art meetings and conference spaces, incredible live and theatrical entertainment experiences, and an extensive array of restaurant, nightlife, and retail offerings. MGM Resorts creates immersive, iconic experiences through its suite of Las Vegas-inspired brands. The MGM Resorts portfolio encompasses 31 unique hotel and destination gaming offerings in the United States and Macau, including some of the most recognizable resort brands in the industry such as Bellagio, MGM Grand, ARIA, and Park MGM. The Company's 50/50 venture, BetMGM, LLC, offers U.S. sports betting and online gaming through market-leading brands, including BetMGM and partypoker. The Company is currently pursuing targeted expansion in Asia through the integrated resort opportunity in Japan. Through its “Focused on What Matters: Embracing Humanity and Protecting the Planet” <a href="https://www.mgmresorts.com/en/company/csr.html" target="_blank">philosophy</a>, MGM Resorts commits to creating a more sustainable future, while striving to make a bigger difference in the lives of its employees, guests, and in the communities where it operates. The global employees of MGM Resorts are proud of their company for being recognized as one of FORTUNE® Magazine's World's Most Admired Companies®. For more information, please visit us at <a href="http://www.mgmresorts.com/" target="_blank">mgmresorts.com</a>. <a target="_blank">Please also connect with us @MGMResortsIntl on </a><a href="https://twitter.com/MGMResortsIntl" target="_blank">Twitter</a> as well as <a href="https://www.facebook.com/mgmresorts" target="_blank">Facebook</a> and <a href="https://www.instagram.com/mgmresortsintl" target="_blank">Instagram</a>. </p><p><b> </b></p><p><b>About Park MGM</b></p><p>Park MGM is the Las Vegas Strip’s first smoke-free resort, offering an intimate hotel experience on a grand scale. Park MGM features 2,700 guest rooms and suites in addition to NoMad Las Vegas’ 293 well-appointed guest rooms and suites on the resort’s top four floors. The resort’s robust culinary program features NoMad Library; L.A. legend Roy Choi’s Korean BBQ concept, Best Friend; Hogsalt Hospitality's renowned Bavette's Steakhouse; and the 40,000-square-foot vibrant Italian marketplace, Eataly, among other dining and cocktail experiences. Dolby Live, the resort’s 5,200-seat entertainment destination, is home to special engagements by Lady Gaga, Bruno Mars, and Aerosmith, among other top artists. Park MGM also is home to On The Record, a unique nightlife concept from LA-based Houston Hospitality. Park MGM and NoMad Las Vegas are located in the heart of The Strip, next to the entertainment and dining neighborhood created by The Park and the 20,000-seat T-Mobile Arena. Park MGM and NoMad Las Vegas are operated by MGM Resorts International (NYSE: MGM). For more information and reservations, visit <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__http:/link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=ELTXiqJ2fGJvEhggrXmQr9FRa0n9-2FenjvriM8H44tkd5oZqNIHidyzCWsKEsj485GJat_wPPF3OduLGu3x5Z4bPcfO3kdZjhyp2zBfJAkWzYPIQbjd7-2Bq3h13zCX1wtKL2-2FmNVZ2Yz-2BSJ7AQ1L4P7Mr6zV52-2FlcWkbsMYSIodHYn6nasPk30PxV3lCsq4Vc0Nzs8eEw8EUoG6-2FIhZqjSAWBthrY0wSb8YqaybVMo-2F7vilOa0Ka6EncSDgxpPwGmF7kFZ-2Fu3TtsiVbL6q6-2Fngpyf96bHNgdw2RISbJUxEqEmDKmvG3sh-2FFVzV6lTR33WTTKY9kPIwTaxxoRoDXCOSBtNTp9h2Jzdf6dPnPr1XQU9RsSxgJWb2hFWJvYV-2FndcfX8V85KY9JwsTB86sTt-2Bp5ietqgzA9mEyOALdbUiFQWX9QYR6BTzm71cncn2-2FFPzr4aVy-2FIiC7NgQMIeGgAroAB0oq6Q-3D-3D__;!!OSzR-JodK1I!Tqan8SEQaoKsuYwyUXVTLlSCQDMeFUzCDtANW712jRcxdgD94D9Jk0Axf69rU0KPBw$" target="_blank">ParkMGM.com</a>, call toll-free at 888-529-4828, or find us on <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__http:/link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=PbjIqWsNhFH50douPoqcSk0fzddGctiVtFtitOp5JREuEuXICYksEFzfDBOpbP9g8k4Z_wPPF3OduLGu3x5Z4bPcfO3kdZjhyp2zBfJAkWzYPIQbjd7-2Bq3h13zCX1wtKL2-2FmNVZ2Yz-2BSJ7AQ1L4P7Mr6zV52-2FlcWkbsMYSIodHYn6nasPk30PxV3lCsq4Vc0Nzs8eEw8EUoG6-2FIhZqjSAWBthrY0wSb8YqaybVMo-2F7vilOa0Ka6EncSDgxpPwGmF7kFZ-2Fu3TtsiVbL6q6-2Fngpyf96bHNgdw2RISbJUxEqEmDKmvGef9xcWZPDTNnm7WerMxJGGBlTQn3NfBcUjBWc9PQM43ZnR543BCKZ6pJB1kzlrmqNPQMJh6NetjBQT4NSdYHHyBYUjiCM8UpNWMSChuRjJa1T-2Ffy11I6KjkPQ33fpl1KXxoyWCTgKIvDgZOAyR92D5WuxP7OrP2DCOAZ1PvFZgg-3D-3D__;!!OSzR-JodK1I!Tqan8SEQaoKsuYwyUXVTLlSCQDMeFUzCDtANW712jRcxdgD94D9Jk0Axf689V-S9Kg$" target="_blank">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__http:/link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=ELTXiqJ2fGJvEhggrXmQryVvOuS-2FQBkTaE-2FlXjLqqDFYLeXV752vIg4Apg4I2PW6kEZo_wPPF3OduLGu3x5Z4bPcfO3kdZjhyp2zBfJAkWzYPIQbjd7-2Bq3h13zCX1wtKL2-2FmNVZ2Yz-2BSJ7AQ1L4P7Mr6zV52-2FlcWkbsMYSIodHYn6nasPk30PxV3lCsq4Vc0Nzs8eEw8EUoG6-2FIhZqjSAWBthrY0wSb8YqaybVMo-2F7vilOa0Ka6EncSDgxpPwGmF7kFZ-2Fu3TtsiVbL6q6-2Fngpyf96bHNgdw2RISbJUxEqEmDKmvHJ5Rgwi5GGq9h7A6-2B-2B85h7p23QDLbYjKrWxiTVCpzJpGQ-2FHK6NMSJgnml-2BD7-2FTkx9-2BeURAj9869-2BSw8vsQlZUdjDVNShbKcobJWcnYo95fDAt2Y0SQq0nWBH0cy5ad8k7-2BqjgCaX4YqOBhSjeYvUU9tn-2FBrawhjopmBj-2BGtShnUw-3D-3D__;!!OSzR-JodK1I!Tqan8SEQaoKsuYwyUXVTLlSCQDMeFUzCDtANW712jRcxdgD94D9Jk0Axf68Z9YvvVA$" target="_blank">Facebook</a>, and <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__http:/link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=ELTXiqJ2fGJvEhggrXmQr1cmOJ-2FiyuAgi4-2FDMIypMMmHMwmZzKd9GGg-2FIkCRkqYapK1P_wPPF3OduLGu3x5Z4bPcfO3kdZjhyp2zBfJAkWzYPIQbjd7-2Bq3h13zCX1wtKL2-2FmNVZ2Yz-2BSJ7AQ1L4P7Mr6zV52-2FlcWkbsMYSIodHYn6nasPk30PxV3lCsq4Vc0Nzs8eEw8EUoG6-2FIhZqjSAWBthrY0wSb8YqaybVMo-2F7vilOa0Ka6EncSDgxpPwGmF7kFZ-2Fu3TtsiVbL6q6-2Fngpyf96bHNgdw2RISbJUxEqEmDKmvEcqHEM-2B1G-2FCZRo8F89-2BrsGqQMn9NR4CrU196m5zT-2B8GAFDsP1y610cQGPJ1dC7pN2S1L-2FOnIA5-2BRayFWV1tC94wPXSy7-2FoTq1NV-2FSnB3YkirEUkZTgzhRZ9pSTIBM19A-2FQhKYKAaIOiXhFySC6yaeV-2BkIXazStOQS8XFFtLv4z9A-3D-3D__;!!OSzR-JodK1I!Tqan8SEQaoKsuYwyUXVTLlSCQDMeFUzCDtANW712jRcxdgD94D9Jk0Axf6-8HAl75w$" target="_blank">Twitter</a>.</p></p><p><a href="https://news.dolby.com/en-WW/203399-dolby-and-mgm-resorts-international-launch-dolby-live-at-park-mgm-bringing-live-music-performances-in-dolby-atmos-to-the-entertainment">View full press release</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>Dolby</name>
      <uri>https://www.dolby.com</uri>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
